Guide to the Clarence Stein papers, 1905-1983.
Stein, Clarence papers
- Series IV. General File
  - Disposal of Greenbelt Towns, 1951-53
    - Greenbelt, 1947, 1952-1953 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      notes, reports, resolutions, outline, plan, correspondence
    - Greenbelt Towns -- Disposal, 1953, 1961, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Greenbelt, Maryland, 1949-1961 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      Roger Willcox, John Egan, David L. Krooth
      notes, drawings, legislative bills, pamphlet, report, drafts, correspondence, resolutions, map, newsletters
  - REGIONAL CITIES, 1951-1953
    - Proposed Book, Regional Cities for America, 1945-1951 (Box 9, Folder 27)
      regional cities
      manuscripts, addresses;, notes
    - "Proposed Book -- Regional Cities for America", 1945-1951 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      The Regional City -- summary papers, Cities to Come Outline
      manuscripts, addresses, notes
    - "The Regional City" (looseleaf), 1953-1955 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      Kitimat, B.C.
      manuscripts, sketches, photographs, diagrams, plans
    - Diagrammatic Studies of Superblock, Neighborhood, and District, 1953-1954, Prepared for Regional Cities and Cities To Coma (Super-block Communities), 1950-1958 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      outlines, drawings, notes
  - Regional City: Outline for book, 1951-1953, File #1
    - Regional Cities -- References and Outline of Book, 1949-1961 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      transportation and cities
      drafts, revisions, outlines
  - Regional City File 2, 1951-1953
    - [Untitled] Regional Cities, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      summary of questions, notes, outline
    - Regional City -- Misc. Material, 1949-1964 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      regional cities, new town planning and development
      Benton MacKaye, Albert Mayer
    - Going Places -- II "Regional Cities" -- Ch. II, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      outline
    - Regional Cities --Program -- 2nd Stage, 1951-1954 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      outlines, notes, revisions, charts
    - Regional City -- Fodd -- Land, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 36)
      reference list, chart, outline
    - [Untitled] Regional City Agriculture, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 37)
      agriculture in a regional city, agricultural economics
      Fritz Butheim
      outline, memo, correspondence
    - Rural Areas Agriculture in a Regional City, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 38)
      Frederick (Fritz) Gutheim, Franklin Thackley (Director of )
      USDA, Bureau of Agricultural Economics
      correspondence, notes, outlines
    - Industry "Regional Cities" -- Ch. V., 1953-1954 (Box 9, Folder 39)
      articles, reprints, outline, notes
    - Market Places "Regional Cities" -- Ch. VI. see addition, 1944-1953 (Box 9, Folder 40)
      Hale Walker (National Housing Agency)
      memos, outlines, correspondence
    - Regional City -- Government, 1951-1953 (Box 9, Folder 41)
      Robert M. Lillibridge (Chief Land planner -- Chicago Land Clearance Commission)
      outline, correspondence, articles
    - Recreation "Regional Cities" -- Ch. VIII, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 42)
      outline and report
    - Health "Regional Cities" Ch. IX, ca. 1935-1953 (Box 9, Folder 43)
      health care, health planning
      Dr. Margaret W. Barnard (Director of District Health Administration, NYC.), Louise Blackham
      Peckham (London health center)
      reports, outlines, correspondence, revisions
    - Health, 1952-1953, undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
      health centers, community health care
    - Health Centers, 1942, 1944, undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
      health centers, Maplewood L.A., California, infirmaries report, physicians service, recreation in War housing
      Charles Butler and Addis on Erdman (Arch Associates)
    - Museums, Theaters, Movies, TV "Regional Cities" Ch. XI, 1948, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 46)
      reports, outline, notes, correspondence
    - Community Activities Facilities Recreation, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 47)
      blueprints
    - Community Activities Recreation Theater Movies Public Welfare B-6, 1943-1947 (Box 9, Folder 48)
      George D. Butler, (National Recreation Association), Arthur Mayer (War Activities Committee), Ralph E. Spear (Am. PW Assoc. )
      notes, reports, correspondence, memos
    - Education and The Community Libraries B-7, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 49)
      Louis Blackham
      reports, outlines
    - C Costs Government Cities B-8, 1943-1944 (Box 9, Folder 50)
      notes, graphs, reports, memos
    - Shopping Centers B-ll, 1934, 1943-1952 (Box 10, Folder 1)
      shopping centers, parking lots
      memos, reports, notes, drawings, outlines, articles
    - L Administration Government, index, B-12, 1943 (Box 10, Folder 2)
      reports, outlines, index
  - CITIES TO COME, 1952
    - "Cities to Come" (looseleaf), 1951-1957, undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
      notebook, manuscripts, revised text (working copy), outlines, drafts, diagrams
    - Cities to Come Outline, 1951-1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
      outlines, revisions, drawings, notes, articles, correspondence
    - Cities To Come Portions, 1955-1960 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      outlines, revisions, drafts
    - Introduction: Cities To Come, 1955-1956 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      drafts and revisions, outlines
    - I. A. Radburn and American Descendants Cities To Come, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - I.A.I. Radburn and American Descendants Baldwin Hills Village, 1943, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
      drafts, outlines, notes
    - I.B. The Radburn Idea, Cities To Come, 1939, 1953-1960, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 9)
      Paul Ritter (architectural engineer)
      articles, bibliography, correspondence, outlines
    - Radburn Idea, IB, Photographs and Diagrams, Cities To Come, 1948, 1955, undated (Box 10, Folder 10)
      general plan
      Towards New Towns In America
      drafts, magazine clippings, maps, charts
    - I.C. Radburn's Predecessors: Cambridge Cities To Come, undated (Box 10, Folder 11)
      book plate, postcard
    - I.C. 3 Central Park, Radburn's Predecessors, Cities To Come, 1949 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - I.D. 3 Chandigar: Radburn Grows Up Cities To Come, 1953-1956 (Box 10, Folder 13)
      E. Maxwell Fry, Albert Mayer
      articles, c. reg.
    - II. A Circulation, Going Places, Cities To Come, 1955-1961, undated (Box 10, Folder 14)
      Henry Faigin, Richard Steiner
      articles, outlines, drafts
    - S.B.C. Parking and Traffic, 1955-1961 (Box 10, Folder 15)
      Homer Hoyt, Herbert Emmerich
      articles, outlines, reports, drafts, revisions, correspondence, press releases
    - Cities To Come: Main Collection Paths Through Paths-- Separation of Roads and Path II-B, 1950-1956 (Box 10, Folder 16)
      going places
      outline, notes
    - II. B Specialization and Separation of Functions, Going Places, C to C, 1955, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 17)
      articles, drafts, outline
    - II. D. Air, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 18)
      air transport
    - III. Modern Communities: Cities To Come, 1953, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - III. 1, 2, 3, Anatomy of Towns, Modern Communities at Different Levels. Cities To Come, 1953-1956 (Box 10, Folder 20)
      anatomy, schools and communities
      outlines, drafts, revisions
    - III. A. Superblock. Modern Communities. Cities To Come, 1944, 1955-1957 (Box 10, Folder 21)
      Mies van der Rohe
      articles, drafts
    - Super-Block Requirements, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 22)
      drafts, outline, notes
    - III.B. Neighborhood. Modern Communities Cities To Come, 1953-1961 (Box 10, Folder 23)
      articles, correspondence, drafts, revisions, outlines
    - III.C. Junior District. Modern Communities Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 24)
      ca. 1954
      manuscript notes
    - III.D. Senior District. Modern Communities Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 25)
      undated
      drawing
    - III.E. Town. Modern Communities, Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 26)
      1955
      book review and chart
    - III.F. Regional City. Modern Communities Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - III.G. 1. Open Spaces. Principles, Modern Communities. Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 28)
      1956, 1960
      clipping, articles
    - III.G. 2. Balanced Communities. Principles, Modern Comm'ties. Cities to C. (Box 10, Folder 29)
      John W. Reps
      1960
    - III.G. 3. Seven Ages of Man in Communities (Mumford) Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 30)
      1949
    - IV. Community Facilities, Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 31)
      1955-1956
      outlines, reference list
    - IV. A. 1. Technological Revolution, Community Facilities, Cities To, Come (Box 10, Folder 32)
      newspaper article, manuscript notes
    - IV. A. 2 Vallingby. Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - IV. A. 3. Limiting Unproductive Travel Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 34)
      arterial highways
      magazine clipping
    - IV. A. 4. Open Spaces. Comm. Facilities Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 35)
      1954, 1956-1958, 1962
      manuscript drafts, articles, outlines, revisions
    - Open Spaces (Box 10, Folder 36)
      Orville Freeman (USDA Secretary), Edward Graham
      1961-1962
      articles, press releases, correspondence, reports
    - IV. B. 2. c High School. Education Comm. Facilities. Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 37)
      1953
    - Regional -- Cities Schools Theater (Box 10, Folder 38)
      1948, 1953, 1956, 1959
      charts, outlines, manuscript notes
    - IV. B. Education. Comm. Facilities Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 39)
      Fred Rosenberg
      1944-1945, 1956-1957
      outlines, manuscript notes, articles
    - IV. B. 1. Radburn, G (Box 10, Folder 40)
      Towns, Village, etc.
      Lewis Wilson, Roger Willcox
      manuscript notes, charts
    - IV. B. 2a. Univ. of Va., Harvard, Oxford, see (Cambridge IV-C-1), Education, Comm. Fac., Cities To C. see Chandigar, IVJ.5.c. (Box 10, Folder 41)
      (Harvard, college and university planning)
      map, article, correspondence
    - IV. C. l.b. Library, Leisure Time Activities, Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 42)
      small libraries
      1963
    - IV-C-1-c. Museums (Box 10, Folder 43)
      1951, 1955-1956, 1962
      manuscript notes, notes, clipping
    - Museums--Theoretical Articles, Design (Box 10, Folder 44)
      1943, 1949, 1952
    - IV.C.l.d. Theater, Movie, Radio, TV Leisure Time Activities, Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 45)
      Walter Kerr
      1933, 1935, 1939, 1943, 1945, 1949, 1950, 1953, 1955-1963
      articles, clippings, manuscript notes, outlines, programs, pamphlet, drawings
    - IV. C. 4. Coordination of Leisure Activities Comm. Fac. Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 46)
      1948, 1953-1954, 1957-1960
      clippings, articles, newsletters, manuscript notes
    - IV. D.I.c. Parks, Radburn Idea Superblock Parks. Paris (Box 10, Folder 47)
      Jane Jacobs
      1956, 1961
      article, report
    - IV. D. 2. Neighborhood Centers, Community Facilities, Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 48)
      1950,1955-1956
      report, notes, articles, manuscript notes
    - IV. E. Commerce: Wholesale, Retail, Service Centers (Box 10, Folder 49)
      1954-1955,, 1959, 1961
      articles, manuscript notes
    - IV. E.I. Office Building Center Community Facilities. Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 50)
      1951, 1956-1957, 1960
      articles, drawings, blueprints, outline
    - IV. E. 2. CF. Rockefeller Center, Pittsb. Business Center, Comm., Fac., Cities To C. (Box 10, Folder 51)
      1953, 1957
    - IV. F. Business. Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 52)
      superblocks
      1951, 1956, 1958
      newsletter, outlines, drawings
    - IV. F. 2. (Box 10, Folder 53)
      Industrial Estate Industry. Comm. Fac., Cities To Come
      1954
    - IV. G.I. Health for New Town -- Kitimat Comm. Facilities, Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 54)
      health services in Kitimat, Great Britain, California, New York City
      1942-1944, 1949, 1952-1953, 1956
      reports, outlines, drawings, articles, blueprint, memos
    - IV. I. 4. Government, Comm. Facilities, Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 55)
      William B. Shore (Information Director, RPA, N.Y.)
      1957-1958, 1961
      reprint, address, manuscript notes, correspondence
    - IV. J. 4. State N.Y. State Offices Campus Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 56)
      Carl W. Larson (Acting New York State Architect)
      1956-1957, 1960
      correspondence, articles, clipping, report, drawing, manuscript notes
    - V-A-1. Cities To Come. Venice (Box 10, Folder 57)
      1957
    - Cities To Come: Vallingby. V-A-2 (Box 10, Folder 58)
      1957, 1960
      manuscript notes, outline, references, article
    - V. F. Industry. Cities To Come (Box 10, Folder 59)
      1955-1957, 1959
    - Industrial Location (Box 10, Folder 60)
      1950, 1955-1956, 1958
      articles, newsletter
    - Business Superblock -- CSS (Kizer) Chapter VI -- Addition (Box 10, Folder 61)
      Benjamin H. Kizer
      1951, undated
      article, outline
    - Clarence Stein -- Suggestions Re Ben Kizer' s An Urban-Office Bid. Superblock August 1951 (Box 10, Folder 62)
      1951, 1959
      article, outline, notes, drawings
    - Costume Institute -- Expansion, 1952 and other (Box 10, Folder 63)
      Edward Stone, architect
      1952, 1956
      outlines, notes, drafts, drawings, correspondence
    - [Untitled] (Box 10, Folder 64)
      Costume Institute proposed expansion plans
    - Costume Museum, 1954 (Box 10, Folder 65)
      expansion
      Edward D. Stone, architect
      1954-1958
      Metropolitan Museum Institute of Costume Design
      press release, pamphlet, clipping, notes, plans
    - 1922-23 Influence of Letchworth in American (written 1953) Travels (Box 10, Folder 66)
      Carl Feiss, Frederic J. Osborn
    - Reg. City and Watershed District, 1954-1955 (Box 10, Folder 67)
      Edward H. Graham (USDA)
      1954-1957
      Plant Technology Division, United States Department of Agriculture
      correspondence, notes, legislative bill, outlines, articles
    - Memo On Planning Education at M.I.T., Nov. 11,1955 (Box 10, Folder 68)
      Catharine Bauer, Gordon Stephenson, Lewis Mumford, J.R. Killian, Jr., (Pres., M.I.T. ), Edwin S. Burdell, (Pres., The Cooper Union), Frederick J. Adams, (Dept. of City and Regional Planning, M.I.T.)
      memos, drafts, revisions, correspondence, clippings, reports
    - [Untitled] (Box 10, Folder 69)
      planning education in New York City
      Albert Mayer, Lawrence M. Orton CNYC Planning Commission)
      1959-1961
      notes, memos, bibliography, correspondence
    - 1956, AIA Gold Medal (Incl. Speech) (Box 10, Folder 70)
      1956
      reprints, speech
  - THE RADBURN IDEA, 1957
    - The Radburn Idea: Preliminary Drafts and Copies (Box 10, Folder 71)
      outlines, drafts, notes
  - THE RADBURN IDEA, 1957
    - Notes For The Radburn Idea (Box 10, Folder 72)
      notes, outline, references
  - THE RADBURN IDEA, 1957
    - Radburn Idea -- VII-57 Notes (Box 10, Folder 73)
  - THE RADBURN IDEA, 1957
    - Cambridge -- Campus (Box 10, Folder 74)
      drafts/ notes, references, article, drawing
  - THE RADBURN IDEA, 1957
    - Pattern For Dispersal, 3rd Copy (Box 10, Folder 75)
    - Appalachian Trail History, 1922 (by Benton MacKaye, 1957) (Box 10, Folder 76)
      article, correspondence
    - Am. Inst. of Planners (AIP), 1958 Distinguished Service Award and Honorary Membership, 1964 (Box 10, Folder 77)
      Henry S. Churchill
      1958, 1964
      citation, notes, correspondence
    - West Side Urban Renewal, 1958-9 (Box 10, Folder 78)
      middle income housing
      Albert Mayer, Chloethiel Woodward Smith
      1956-1959
      proposal, notes, reports, correspondence clippings, drafts, drawing
    - Proposed Research, 1959 Design Project In Large Scale Housing Stein and Mayer (Box 10, Folder 79)
      Ira Robbins (NYC Housing Authority), Thomas B. Thompson (PHA, Housing and Home Finance Agency), William Raid (NYC Housing Authority), Alexander Bing
      1959-1963
      New York City Housing Authority, Housing and Home Finance Agency
      correspondence, application, memos, notes
    - CSS Ebenezer Howard Medal. 1960 (Box 10, Folder 80)
      Wyndham Thomas, Town and Country Planning Assoc., F. J. Osborn
      1959-1960
      Council of the Town and Country Planning Association
      program, correspondence, memos, clipping
    - Federal Dept. of Urban and Regional Development, Oct. 1961 (Box 10, Folder 81)
      Sen. Joseph S. Clark, Dennis O'Harrow, Ed Bacon
      1961
      notes, proposal, correspondence, drafts, revisions, memos, legislative bill copy, Presidential message
    - Resources For The Future, 1961 Incl. CSS's "Control and Design of Metropolitan Growth and Development" (Box 10, Folder 82)
      Tracy B. Augur, Joseph Fisher, RFF
      drafts, correspondence, prospectus, notes
    - A Business Superblock, 1961 (based on Kizer) w. diagrams (Box 10, Folder 83)
      drawings, diagrams, drafts
    - Small Parks For New York City, 1962-3 (Box 10, Folder 84)
      West Side renewal
      Simon Breines, James Felt
      Committee on Open Spaces, Citizens' Housing and Planning Council
      outline, correspondence, drafts, revisions, notes, pamphlet
    - [Untitled] (Box 10, Folder 85)
      Small Parks in NYC, playgrounds
      George Butler
      1962
      National Recreation Association
      notes, correspondence, drafts, articles, clippings
    - Open Spaces (Box 10, Folder 86)
      California, New York Legislation
      Karl J. Belser (Director, Santa Clara County Planning Dept.), Catherine Bauer Wurster
      correspondence, clipping, memo, legislative bills
- Series V. Research File
  - Toward New Towns for America, C. Stein, University Press of Liverpool, Chicago, Illinois, 1951, autograph by C. Stein (Box 11, Volume 1)
  - Coordinated Planned Development, typed May 2, 1963
    - Proposal for Increased Coordination in Planned Development, N.Y.C.: Last Draft (4-IV-63) (Box 11, Folder 1)
      planned development in NYC, London County, Stockholm, Milwaukee
      A. I. A. Urban Design Committee
      drafts, outlines, notes, articles, newsletters
  - Coordinated Planned Development
    - [Untitled] (Box 11, Folder 2)
      planning, N.Y.C., large scale housing, community districts
      1949, 1964
      Citizens Union, Citizens' Housing and Planning Council of NYC, AIA Comm. on Housing
      2 reports
  - Coordinated Planned Development
    - New York State Development Coordinator, Early Drafts (Box 11, Folder 3)
      Benton MacKaye, George H. Hallett, Jr., Albert Mayer
      1958-1959, 1961, 1964
      memos, articles, proposals, correspondence
  - Coordinated Planned Development
    - N.Y. State Defense Communities Law Proposed (Hallett, July 1951) (Box 11, Folder 1)
      Lee F. Johnson (Exec. V.P., NHC, Inc.), Paul Oppermann, George Hallett (Citizens Union)
      1950-1951
      Citizens Union, National Housing Conference,
      correspondence, notes, legislative bill
  - Coordinated Planned Development
    - New York State Division of Planned Development, Desmond Bill -- 1948-58 (Box 11, Folder 5)
      Gov. Thomas E. Dewey
      1943, 1948, 1958
      correspondence, notes, legislative bills
  - Coordinated Plained Development
    - State Planning -- New York -- Schenectady Sp. [speech] (Box 11, Folder 6)
      Ira S. Robbins, George H. Hallett, Jr.
      1948, 1951
      New York State Land Agency, Freedom Forum
      notes, reference, correspondence, articles
  - Coordinated Planned Development
    - N.Y.S. Regional Development, 1964 N.Y. State Plan (Box 11, Folder 7)
      Frederick E. Wiedle, N.Y. State Office for Regional Development
      ca. 1926, 1958-1959, 1961, 1964
      New York State Office for Regional Development
      notes, diagrams, clippings, outlines, correspondence, drafts
  - Coordinated Planned Development, 1963 Gen.
    - Urban Redevelopment (Box 11, Folder 8)
      urban design, planning, renewal
      William Slayton (Commissioner of Urban Renewal Administration), Arthur Ling, Charles Abrams, Charles Brown
      1956-1957, 1959-1963
      articles, reprints
  - Planned Development, 1963 Gen.
    - N.Y. Times Article Metropolitan Government; Metropolitan (Box 11, Folder 9)
      transportation, suburbs, urban sprawl, government
      Gordon Stephenson, William H. Whyte, Jr., Jane Jacobs
      1955-1960, 1963, undated
      articles, clipping, photographs
  - Planned Development, 1963 Gen.
    - Research and The Future (Box 11, Folder 10)
      metropolitan region research
      John T. Brown
      Regional Science Association
      papers
  - Planned Development, 1963 Gen.
    - Dispersal of Industry and Offices (Box 11, Folder 11)
      commuter problems, office and industrial dispersal
      1948, 1953, 1956-1957, 1959-1960
      articles, notes
  - Planned Development, 1963 Gen.
    - Breakdown of Our Cities, N.Y. June 14/61 (Box 11, Folder 12)
      real estate, blackouts
      news clippings, article
  - Planned Development, 1963 Gen.
    - Land, Redevelopment, Urban Renewal, Suburbs, (USA) Postwar Physical Development (Box 11, Folder 13)
      Norman Pearson, Nathan Glazer, Henry Churchill, Hans Blumenfeld, Carl Feiss, Robert C. Weinburg
  - Planned Development, 1963 Gen.
    - Auto--Courts and Cul-de-Sac, also Garden Courts (Box 11, Folder 14)
      1955, undated
      drawings, articles, notes
    - "New Towns Policy -- Newark Group -- 1963-64" (Box 11, Folder 15)
      Carl Feiss, Albert Mayer
      1963-1964
      The Newark Group
      correspondence, reports
    - "1965 -- Radburn -- N.J. Home Builders Association" (Box 11, Folder 16)
      Radburn, N. J., N.J. Home Builders award
      1965
      New Jersey Home Builders Association
      magazine, correspondence
    - "AIA N.Y. Chapter -- Andrew J. Thomas Award 1967" (Box 11, Folder 17)
      awards and honors
      1967
      correspondence, typed copy of award
    - "Wright, Henry, Distribution of His Papers -- Gen. Files, 1967" (Box 11, Folder 18)
      Henry Wright
      1967-1968
    - "AIP 50th Anniversary Award -- 1967" (Box 11, Folder 19)
      American Institute of Planners
  - CSS Early and Later Writings Unpublished
    - "I (unpublished) CSS writings--to 1919" (Box 11, Folder 20)
      early housing, housing problems, neighborhood and city planning, Regional Plan of New York
      Charles Whitaker
      1905-1919
      manuscripts, correspondence
  - Writings and Articles (unpublished)
    - "II 1920' s" (Box 11, Folder 21)
      housing problems, N.Y.C.
      Henry Wright, Alexander Bing
      1905, 1915, 1920-1929
      manuscripts, notes, outlines
  - Early Writings and Articles (unpublished)
    - "Ill New Communities, 1930-31" (Box 11, Folder 22)
      building new communities, Regional Cities, Sunnyside, new communities
      1926, 1930, 1931
      typescripts, carbon copies, outline, notes, chapters I and II, press release
  - Writings arid Articles (unpublished)
    - "IV Outline Community Housing, 1931/32" (Box 11, Folder 23)
      housing, new community planning
      1931, 1932
      carbon copy, manuscripts, outline, drafts
  - Writings and Articles (unpublished)
    - "V -- 1930' s continued" (Box 11, Folder 24)
      housing, communities, regional cities, "Rebuild America"
      Henry W right, Catherine H. Bauer, Elizabeth Colt
      1930, 1934
      Pres. Hoover Comm. on Large Scale Operation
      manuscripts, book proposal, outline, drafts, revisions, notes, correspondence
  - Writings and Articles (unpublished)
    - "VI. Misc. unfinished work (or unpublished)" (Box 11, Folder 25)
      housing, planned development, garden cities, Going Places, Building New Communities
      1924, 1939-1955
      manuscripts, notes, book outlines
  - Writings and Articles (unpublished)
    - "VI Misc. unfinished work (or unpublished) (Box 11, Folder 26)
      Greenbelt towns, New Towns, dispersal in war and peace, AIP reviews, AIA convention
      1939-1955
  - Early Writings and Articles (unpublished)